"Choking to death.
Woot, woot."
(Theatre staff:)Guys, I am sorry.
We are full up.
(Sheldon:)No!
(Theatre staff:)We're full up.
(Leonard:)We really want
to see this.
Isn't there anything
you can do?
(Theatre staff:)Sorry. Fire regulations.
Should've gotten here earlier.
(Sheldon:)This is nothing but a
blatant abuse of power
(Sheldon:)by a petty functionary.
(Sheldon:)Explain to me why
Wil Wheaton and his lackeys
(Sheldon:)get in and we don't.
'Cause I'm the petty functionary
with a clipboard, bitch.
(Howard:)I guess that's that.
(Howard:)Let's go home.
(Sheldon:)You know what?
(Sheldon:)I'm going back to
"I told you so."
(Sheldon:)I told you so.
(Raj:)We can still see something.
Oh, the new Sandra Bullock movie
is playing two blocks away.
(Raj:)You know Sandy B.
always brings it.
(Sheldon:)Look-- a side door.
(Sheldon:)Come on, Short Round.
(Howard:)I guess we'd better
go after him.
(Leonard:)Short Round?
Indy's young sidekick
from Temple of Doom.